choosing health insurance can be tricky
especially when you're looking for a
plan that not only covers medical
expenses but also gives you some returns
so it's important to have coverage but
getting something extra back for your
payments is a bonus so this is not for
financial advice it's for educational
purposes only so in this video I'll
share five health insurance plans that
offer Returns on premiums so first max
bua health insurance provides plans
where you can get a return a return if
you don't make any claims the second is
star health insurance which offers great
returns and excellent
coverage the third is religare health
insurance which offers policies that
reward you with returns if you stay
healthy and claim free the fourth is
HDFC Ergo health insurance which is
known for its great coverage and
premiums returns after a claim free year
lastly ICICI lumbar provides great
health insurance with an option to get
returns if you don't use the insurance
so getting the right health insurance
coverage you know it gives you back a
great way to protect your future Take
Action Now find the right plan for
yourself I'll put these in the
description so you can narrow it down
check them out one by one it's not going
to take you long to find the best one
for you leave me a like love you